export const quizdata = [
    {
        question: "Q1: What Is the full form of HTML?",
        a: "Hello my Friens",
        b: "Hire of Me",
        c: "Hello My System",
        d: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        ans: "ans4"
    },
    {
        question: "Q2: What Is the full form of HTML?",
        a: "Hello my Friens",
        b: "Hire of Me",
        c: "Hello My System",
        d: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        ans: "ans3"
    },
    {
        question: "Q3: What Is the full form of HTML?",
        a: "Hello my Friens",
        b: "Hire of Me",
        c: "Hello My System",
        d: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        ans: "ans1"
    },
    {
        question: "Q4: What Is the full form of HTML?",
        a: "Hello my Friens",
        b: "Hire of Me",
        c: "Hello My System",
        d: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        ans: "ans3"
    },
    {
        question: "Q5: What Is the full form of HTML?",
        a: "Hello my Friens",
        b: "Hire of Me",
        c: "Hello My System",
        d: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        ans: "ans4"
    },
    {
        question: "Q6: What Is the full form of HTML?",
        a: "Hello my Friens",
        b: "Hire of Me",
        c: "Hello My System",
        d: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        ans: "ans3"
    },
    {
        question: "Q7 What is the Full form of HTML?",
        a: "Hello my Friens",
        b: "Hire of Me",
        c: "Hello My System",
        d: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        ans: "ans4"
    },
    {
        question: "Q8 What Is the full form of HTML?",
        a: "Hello my Friens",
        b: "Hire of Me",
        c: "Hello My System",
        d: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        ans: "ans4"
    },
    {
        question: "Q9 What Is the full form of HTML?",
        a: "Hello my Friens",
        b: "Hire of Me",
        c: "Hello My System",
        d: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        ans: "ans1"
    },
    {
        question: "Q10 What Is the full form of HTML?",
        a: "Hello my Friens",
        b: "Hire of Me",
        c: "Hello My System",
        d: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        ans: "ans1"
    },
]